A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Office of the Vice President of Administration, Office Files of Arthur D. Trottenberg FA669
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Financial, 1958-1980; 1970-1975; III
  - Budget
    - General Management Costs - FY 1969, 1968 January - July (Box 19, Folder 174)
    - General Management Costs - FY 1969, 1968 July - December (Box 20, Folder 175)
    - General Management Costs - FY 1971, 1970 February - November (Box 20, Folder 176)
    - General Management Costs - FY 1972, 1971 February - 1973 January (Box 20, Folder 177)
    - General Management Costs - FY 1973, 1972 February - 1973 October (Box 20, Folder 178)
    - General Management Costs - FY 1974, 1972 November - 1974 August (Box 20, Folder 179)
    - Division of Administration - FY 1970, 1970 August (Box 20, Folder 180)
    - Division of Administration - FY 1972, 1971 April, 1972 April (Box 20, Folder 181)
    - Division of Administration - FY 1973, 1972 March - November (Box 20, Folder 182)
    - Comptroller - FY 1969-1970, 1968 November - 1969 September (Box 20, Folder 183)
    - Comptroller - FY 1971, 1970 July - August (Box 20, Folder 184)
    - Manpower Services - FY 1969, 1968 November - 1969 April (Box 20, Folder 185)
    - Manpower Services - FY 1971-1972, 1971 April - 1973 January (Box 20, Folder 186)
    - Manpower Services - FY 1973, 1972 March - May (Box 20, Folder 187)
    - Logistical Services - FY 1970-1971, 1968 June - 1970 August (Box 20, Folder 188)
    - Logistical Services - FY 1973, 1972 July - August (Box 20, Folder 189)
    - Program-Related Investments - FY 1970-1971, 1968 November - 1971 November (Box 20, Folder 190)
    - Program-Related Investments - FY 1973, 1972 February - September (Box 21, Folder 191)
    - Office of Reports - FY 1973, 1972 April 14 (Box 21, Folder 192)
    - Program Management Costs - FY 1971, 1969 December - 1972 March (Box 21, Folder 193)
    - Program Management Costs - FY 1971, 1970 April - 1971 December (Box 21, Folder 194)
    - Program Management Costs - FY 1972, 1971 February - 1973 January (Box 21, Folder 195)
    - Program Management Costs - FY 1973, 1972 February - 1973 March (Box 21, Folder 196)
    - Program Management Costs - FY 1974-1975, 1972 February - 1973 February (Box 21, Folder 197)
    - Program Management Costs - FY 1974-1975, 1973 February - 1974 February (Box 21, Folder 198)
    - Division of the Humanities and the Arts - FY 1970, 1969 April 14 (Box 21, Folder 199)
    - Division of Education and Research - FY 1970, 1968 December - 1969 May (Box 21, Folder 200)
    - Division of Education and Research - FY 1971-1972, 1970 April 22 (Box 21, Folder 201)
    - Office of Public Broadcasting - FY 1970-1971, 1969 May - 1970 April (Box 22, Folder 202)
    - Division of National Affairs - FY 1970, 1969 April - November (Box 22, Folder 203)
    - Division of National Affairs - FY 1973, 1972 February (Box 22, Folder 204)
    - Division of International Affairs - FY 1970, 1969 March - July (Box 22, Folder 205)
    - Budget Reports, 1968-1972 (Box 22, Folder 206)
- Personnel, 1958-1980; 1968-1978; IV
  The General subseries consists of documents on a number of topics, such as staff recruitment and orientation, leaves of absence, housing assistance, and travel policy. The Compensation subseries contains information on salary policy and benefits (mainly the thrift and retirement plans). The series consists of memoranda, correspondence, reports, policy papers, charts, and notes.
  Series IV, Personnel, is housed in eight archival boxes, and is divided into two subseries: General and Compensation. Items within each folder are arranged chronologically, maintaining original order.
  Personnel The Personnel series covers a wide range of topics, such as the internationalization of staff, staff recruitment and orientation, leaves of absence, housing assistance, travel policy, and field office memos. However, the most abundant information that this series contains is that of compensation packages, ranging from salary policies to benefits. Whereas salary policy is primarily documented in the form of office memoranda, much of the information on benefits is in the form of consultant reports by Towers, Perrin, Forster, and Crosby (TPF&C). Establishing salary policies during the early 1970s was a difficult task due to the rapidly rising costs of living in New York combined with the Foundation's need to cut management costs during its period of severe retrenchment. During Trottenberg's time, employee benefit packages were affected by the Employment Retirement Income Security Act of 1974, which will be discussed in more depth later.
  - General
    - General, 1966-1967 (Box 22, Folder 207)
    - General, 1968-1969 (Box 22, Folder 208)
    - General, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 209)
    - General, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 210)
    - General, 1972 January-April (Box 22, Folder 211)
    - General, 1972 May-December (Box 22, Folder 212)
    - General, 1973-1975 (Box 22, Folder 213)
    - Field Office Memos, 1970-1972 (Box 23, Folder 214)
    - Field Office Memos, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 215)
    - Field Office Memos, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 216)
    - Job Description Study, 1964-1974 (Box 23, Folder 217)
    - Staff Recruitment, 1963-1966 (Box 23, Folder 218)
    - Staff Recruitment, 1969-1974 (Box 23, Folder 219)
    - Employment Tests, 1962-1970 (Box 23, Folder 220)
    - Personnel Development and Training, 1954 (Box 23, Folder 220a)
    - New Staff Orientation, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 221)
    - Staff Profile, 1971-1973 (Box 23, Folder 222)
    - Internationalization of Staff, 1969-1970 (Box 23, Folder 223)
    - Staff Programs, 1971-1979 (Box 23, Folder 224)
    - Delegation of Authority, 1958-1968 (Box 23, Folder 225)
    - Check Cashing, 1972-1973 (Box 23, Folder 226)
    - Leaves of Absence, 1969-1974 (Box 23, Folder 227)
    - Educational Programs, 1972-1980 (Box 24, Folder 228)
    - Grievance Procedure, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 229)
    - Staff Appraisals, 1971-1977 (Box 24, Folder 230)
    - Job Reclassifications and Promotions, 1964-1972 (Box 24, Folder 231)
    - Termination of Employment, 1968-1971 (Box 24, Folder 232)
    - Holidays, 1968-1970 (Box 24, Folder 233)
    - Health and Medical Services, 1967-1972 (Box 24, Folder 234)
    - Cost of Living, 1969-1978 (Box 24, Folder 235)
    - Housing Assistance for NY Staff, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 236)
    - Facility Charges, 1969-1974 (Box 24, Folder 237)
    - Moving and Shipping, 1968-1977 (Box 24, Folder 238)
    - Automobiles, 1968-1972 (Box 24, Folder 239)
    - Insurances, 1973-1975 (Box 24, Folder 240)
    - Insurances, 1976-1979 (Box 24, Folder 241)
    - John Liner Associates, Inc., 1971 (Box 25, Folder 242)
    - Travel, general, 1965-1969 (Box 25, Folder 243)
    - Travel, general, 1970 January-June (Box 25, Folder 244)
    - Travel, general, 1970 July-December (Box 25, Folder 245)
    - Travel, general, 1971-1975 (Box 25, Folder 246)
    - Travel, spouses, 1969-1970 (Box 25, Folder 247)
    - Travel, spouses, 1971-1976 (Box 25, Folder 248)
    - Travel, freight and allowances, 1969-1972 (Box 25, Folder 249)
    - Cresap, McCormick and Paget, Inc., 1975 (Box 25, Folder 250)
  - Compensation
    - Salary Policy - FY 1972, 1971 July - December (Box 26, Folder 251)
    - Salary Policy - FY 1973, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 252)
    - Salary Policy - FY 1974, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 253)
    - Salary Policy - FY 1975, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 254)
    - Salary Policy - FY 1976, 1975 June - 1976 June (Box 26, Folder 255)
    - Salary Policy - FY 1977, 1976 April - September (Box 26, Folder 256)
    - Salary Policy - FY 1978, 1977 March - October (Box 26, Folder 257)
    - Salary Policy - FY 1979, 1978 April - November (Box 26, Folder 258)
    - Salary Policy - FY 1980, 1979 March - September (Box 26, Folder 259)
    - Salary Comparisons, 1970-1976 (Box 26, Folder 260)
    - Pay Board Regulations, 1971-1973 (Box 26, Folder 261)
    - Benefits, general, 1966-1973 (Box 26, Folder 262)
    - Thrift and Retirement Plan, 1969-1975 (Box 26, Folder 263)
    - Webster, Sheffield, Fleischmann, Hitchcock & Brookfield, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 264)
    - Rogers, Casey, & Barksdale, Inc., 1977 (Box 27, Folder 265)
    - Robert Hayes and Associates, Inc., 1978 (Box 27, Folder 266)
    - Towers, Perrin, Forster & Crosby (TPF&C Reports), 1968 (Box 27, Folder 267)
    - Towers, Perrin, Forster & Crosby (TPF&C Report), 1969 February (Box 27, Folder 268)
    - Towers, Perrin, Forster & Crosby (TPF&C Appendices), 1969 February (Box 27, Folder 269)
    - Towers, Perrin, Forster & Crosby (TPF&C Report), 1969 April (Box 27, Folder 270)
    - Towers, Perrin, Forster & Crosby (TPF&C Report), 1970 September (Box 27, Folder 271)
    - Towers, Perrin, Forster & Crosby (TPF&C Report), 1970 December (Box 27, Folder 272)
    - Towers, Perrin, Forster & Crosby (TPF&C Report), 1971 (Box 28, Folder 273)
    - Towers, Perrin, Forster & Crosby (TPF&C Report), 1972 May (Box 28, Folder 274)
    - Towers, Perrin, Forster & Crosby (TPF&C Report), 1972 October (Box 28, Folder 275)
    - Towers, Perrin, Forster & Crosby (TPF&C Reports), 1973 January-June (Box 28, Folder 276)
    - Towers, Perrin, Forster & Crosby (TPF&C Reports), 1973 October-December (Box 28, Folder 277)
    - Towers, Perrin, Forster & Crosby (TPF&C Reports), 1974 (Box 28, Folder 278)
    - Towers, Perrin, Forster & Crosby (TPF&C Reports), 1975 (Box 28, Folder 279)
    - Towers, Perrin, Forster & Crosby (TPF&C Reports), 1977 May-September (Box 28, Folder 280)
    - Towers, Perrin, Forster & Crosby (TPF&C Report), 1971 November (Box 28, Folder 281)
    - Towers, Perrin, Forster & Crosby (TPF&C Report), 1978 February (Box 29, Folder 282)
    - Towers, Perrin, Forster & Crosby (TPF&C Report), 1978 September (Box 29, Folder 283)
    - Review of Personnel and Employee Benefit Practices for Local Staff - Towers, Perrin, Forster & Crosby (TPF&C Reports), 1970; 20x24 box. (Box 65)
- Information Systems and Services, 1967-1983; 1967-1977; V
  The General subseries consists of general consultant studies on the Foundation's information systems and services. The Library subseries and the Archives and Records Management subseries are fairly limited in the information on these units. The Computer and Electronic Data Processing subseries, on the other hand, is a more useful subseries as it more thoroughly documents computer usage within the Foundation, particularly in its early stages. The series consists of memoranda, correspondence, reports, policy papers, reports, and notes.
  Series V, Information Systems and Services, is housed in four archival boxes, and is divided into four subseries: General, Library, Archives and Records Management, and Computer and Electronic Data Processing. Items within each folder are arranged chronologically, maintaining original order.
  Information Systems and Services The Information Systems and Services series addresses the full gamut of information areas of the Foundation. The Library subseries includes limited information about library usage, donation of books, and future development of the library and library services. The Archives and Records Management subseries contains information on record-keeping and records management in the form of correspondence control and bureaucratic reporting, as well as information on an oral history project documenting policies, program objectives, and organization of the Foundation. The subseries also documents the beginnings of the Foundation's archives, primarily in the form of establishing policies and procedures on the access of archival records. The series proves most useful in the fullness of its Computer and Electronic Data Processing subseries. Information technology is no doubt an integral part of today's workplace, but its presence was not always assumed. The Computer and Electronic Data Processing subseries documents the Foundation's early efforts at incorporating use of computer systems into the Foundation's workload in order to speed up processes that could easily be automated. Initially (as early as 1965), the Foundation looked into the prospect of using computers primarily for computer-based accounting. However, as years passed, the Foundation expanded its interest in computer usage, as with its 1974 proposal for the Grants Retrieval and Information Display System (GRIDS), providing wider-spread access of data on grants throughout the Foundation.
  - General
    - Documentation Incorporated, part 1, 1967 March (Box 29, Folder 284)
    - Documentation Incorporated, part 2, 1967 March (Box 29, Folder 285)
    - Documentation Incorporated, part 3, 1967 March (Box 29, Folder 286)
    - Documentation Incorporated, 1967 April (Box 29, Folder 287)
    - Cresap, McCormick and Paget, 1973 (Box 29, Folder 288)
  - Library
    - Library, general, 1968-1969 (Box 30, Folder 289)
    - Library, general, 1970-1974 (Box 30, Folder 290)
    - Library Committee, 1968-1969 (Box 30, Folder 291)
    - Donation of Books, 1972-1974 (Box 30, Folder 292)
    - Donation to JFK Library, 1973 (Box 30, Folder 293)
  - Archives and Records Management
    - Archives, general, 1970-1983 (Box 30, Folder 294)
    - Lektrievers – Records' Security and Access, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 295)
    - Oral History, 1970-1977 (Box 30, Folder 296)
    - Bureaucratic Reporting, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 297)
    - Correspondence Control, 1967-1973 (Box 30, Folder 298)
    - Outside Money Managers, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 299)
    - Towers, Perrin, Forster, and Crosby, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 300)
  - Computer and Electronic Data Processing
    - Computer, general, 1965-1967 (Box 30, Folder 301)
    - Computer, general, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 302)
    - Computer, general, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 303)
    - Computer, general, 1970 (Box 31, Folder 304)
    - Computer, general, 1971-1972 (Box 31, Folder 305)
    - Computer, general, 1973 (Box 31, Folder 306)
    - Computer, general, 1974 (Box 31, Folder 307)
    - Computer, general, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 308)
    - Computer, general, 1976-1977 (Box 31, Folder 309)
    - Computer Advisory Committee, 1969-1970 (Box 31, Folder 310)
    - Computer Services Committee, 1976 (Box 31, Folder 311)
    - Computer Budget Reports, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 312)
    - Computer Status Reports, 1969-1973 (Box 31, Folder 313)
    - Automated Payroll and Personnel Information System, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 314)
    - Automated Portfolio Management and Securities Accounting, 1970-1973 (Box 31, Folder 315)
    - Grants Retrieval and Information Display System, 1974-1975 (Box 32, Folder 316)
    - Equipment Lease, 1970-1975 (Box 32, Folder 317)
    - IBM, Computer Usage Seminar, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 318)
    - IBM, Equipment, 1975-1976 (Box 32, Folder 319)
    - Center for Management Technology, Inc., 1975-1976 (Box 32, Folder 320)
    - Center for Management Technology, Inc., 1976 (Box 32, Folder 321)
- Overseas, 1966-1979; 1968-1977; VI
  The General subseries consists of documents on a number of topics, including personnel policies, compensation, and taxes for overseas offices, as well as information on specific field offices. The series consists of memoranda, telegrams, reports, policy papers, audits, newspaper articles, and notes.
  Series VI, Overseas, is housed in four archival boxes, and is divided into four subseries: General, Staff Trips, Audits, and Conferences. Items within each folder are arranged chronologically, maintaining original order.
  Overseas The Overseas series covers a number of topics, ranging from compensation and taxes for overseas staff members, to information about field offices such as financial audits. The series also includes staff members' overseas trip reports. For instance, Trottenberg traveled all over the globe to such locales as, London, Paris, Latin American, Egypt, Lebanon, and Nigeria, visiting field offices and attending committee meetings. The series also documents preparation and planning for a number of conferences that were held overseas. Some such conferences include the International Division Conferences in 1973 and 1975, the Athens Press Conference in 1973, as well as conferences held in Nairobi, New Delhi, and Mexico.
  - General
    - Overseas, general, 1969-1973 (Box 32, Folder 322)
    - International Division Organization, 1970 (Box 32, Folder 323)
    - Guidelines to Personnel Administration, 1966 (Box 32, Folder 324)
    - Personnel Policies, 1970-1976 (Box 32, Folder 325)
    - Towers, Perrin, Forster & Crosby, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 326)
    - Towers, Perrin, Forster & Crosby, 1977 (Box 32, Folder 327)
    - Compensation and Taxes, 1974-1976 (Box 32, Folder 328)
    - Compensation and Taxes, 1977 January-August (Box 33, Folder 329)
    - Compensation and Taxes, 1977 September-December (Box 33, Folder 330)
    - Taxes, 1969-1974 (Box 33, Folder 331)
    - Taxes, 1978-1979 (Box 33, Folder 332)
    - Field Office – Athens, Greece, 1970-1972 (Box 33, Folder 333)
    - Field Office – Bangkok, Thailand, 1967 (Box 33, Folder 334)
    - Field Office – Lagos, Nigeria, 1969-1970 (Box 33, Folder 335)
    - Field Office – Madrid, Spain, 1970-1972 (Box 33, Folder 336)
    - Field Office – New Delhi, India, 1968-1975 (Box 33, Folder 337)
    - Field Office – Latin America and Caribbean, 1968-1972 (Box 33, Folder 338)
    - Towers, Perrin, Forster & Crosby – Middle East & Africa, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 339)
    - Towers, Perrin, Forster & Crosby – Asia & Pacific, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 340)
    - Towers, Perrin, Forster & Crosby – Latin America, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 341)
    - Annual Reports, general - FY 1969, 1970 January - February (Box 34, Folder 342)
    - Annual Reports, Middle East and Africa - FY 1968, 1969 January (Box 34, Folder 343)
  - Staff Trips
    - Staff Trips, general, 1968-1970 (Box 34, Folder 344)
    - Asian and Pacific Office Visits, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 345)
    - ADT's Trip to Lebanon, Egypt, and Nigeria, 1968 (Box 34, Folder 346)
    - ADT's Trip to Latin America, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 347)
    - ADT's Trip to Paris, France and London, England, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 348)
  - Audits of Field Offices
    - Stewart, Charles and John V. McDermott, 1966 (Box 34, Folder 349)
    - Akmajian, Herant, 1969-1971 (Box 34, Folder 350)
    - Wolf, Thomas and John P. Doran, 1971 (Box 34, Folder 351)
    - Masone Jr., Nunzio, Thomas Wolf, and Leonard Spilka, 1972 (Box 34, Folder 352)
    - Esola, Ronald, 1972 (Box 34, Folder 353)
    - Akmajian, Herant, 1972-1973 (Box 34, Folder 354)
    - Wolf, Thomas, Leonard Spilka, and Ronald P. Walker, 1973-1975 (Box 34, Folder 355)
    - Masone Jr., Nunzio, Ronald Esola, and Thomas Wolf, 1973-1975 (Box 35, Folder 356)
  - Conferences
    - Administrative Conferences, 1968-1971 (Box 35, Folder 357)
    - International Division Conference, 1973 (Box 35, Folder 358)
    - International Division Conference, 1975 (Box 35, Folder 359)
    - Nairobi Conference, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 360)
    - Mexico Conference, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 361)
    - New Delhi, India Conference, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 362)
    - New Delhi Conference, 1971 (Box 35, Folder 363)
    - New Delhi Conference, 1971 (Box 35, Folder 364)
    - Athens Press Conference, 1973 (Box 35, Folder 365)
- Program Activity, 1958-1979; 1968-1977; VII
  Specific appropriations have been removed from the folders as this information can be found within the dockets in the Board of Trustees Records. Moreover, information about various PRIs has also been removed and was originally found in the Closed Grant File Room at Ford Foundation (see Appendix E).
  The General subseries consists of information on planning and evaluation the Foundation's programs. The Program-Related Investments focuses on the progress of the PRI program in its first years, and the Grants subseries emphasizes Foundation policies on administering grants. The series consists of memoranda, correspondence, reports, financial reviews, and notes.
  Series VII, Program Activity, is housed in six archival boxes, and is divided into four subseries: General, Program-Related Investments, Grants, Financial Reviews of Grantees. Items within each folder are arranged chronologically, maintaining original order.
  Program Activity The Program Activity series documents general policy for activities related to the Foundation's program areas. The series covers general program strategy, planning and evaluation. It also covers topics in grant administration such as, travel and study awards, payment policy, multi-year renewals, Delegated Authority Projects (DAPs), Foundation-Administered Projects (FAPs), and expenditure responsibility. The series contains some information on specific grants that the Foundation issued in the form of financial reviews of grantees. The series also documents Program-Related Investments (PRIs), a direct responsibility of Trottenberg's. Beginning in 1968, PRIs began as an experiment in realizing philanthropic goals via capital investment. The PRI subseries documents the beginnings of this experiment, covering some specific information on PRI recipients to self-evaluation of the new program. Topics in this series include the PRI Policy Committee, threshold approvals, fiscal status summaries, and investment summaries. The series also includes two information papers evaluating the PRI program two years and four years after its inception.
  - General
    - Program Strategy, 1968 (Box 36, Folder 366)
    - Program Planning, 1972 (Box 36, Folder 367)
    - Program Evaluation, 1968 (Box 36, Folder 368)
    - Monitoring Policy, 1970-1971 (Box 36, Folder 369)
  - Program-Related Investments
    - PRI Meetings, 1968-1971 (Box 36, Folder 370)
    - Mutual Fund Meeting, 1968-1969 (Box 36, Folder 371)
    - Investments, general, 1969-1973 (Box 36, Folder 372)
    - Commitments, revisions, 1968-1970 (Box 36, Folder 373)
    - Threshold Approvals, 1969-1971 (Box 36, Folder 374)
    - Investment Summaries and Annual Reports, 1968-1970 (Box 36, Folder 375)
    - Fiscal Status and Summary Reports, 1970-1972 (Box 36, Folder 376)
    - Information Paper – 2 Years of PRIs, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 377)
    - Information Paper – 4 Years of PRIs, 1971-1972 (Box 36, Folder 378)
    - Webster, Sheffield, Fleischmann, Hitchcock & Brookfield, 1968 (Box 36, Folder 379)
    - Marshall and MacDevitt, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 380)
  - Grants
    - Grants, general, 1958-1973 (Box 37, Folder 381)
    - Grants to Individuals, 1969-1971 (Box 37, Folder 382)
    - Grants to Individuals, 1972-1974 (Box 37, Folder 383)
    - Grants to Individuals, 1975-1977 (Box 37, Folder 384)
    - Travel and Study Awards, 1968-1969 (Box 37, Folder 385)
    - Grants to Government Employees, 1969-1977 (Box 37, Folder 386)
    - Grants Processing System, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 387)
    - Payment Policy and Procedures, 1970-1976 (Box 38, Folder 388)
    - Overhead Charges, 1968-1970 (Box 38, Folder 389)
    - Overhead Charges, 1971-1974 (Box 38, Folder 390)
    - Expenditure Responsibility, 1969-1979 (Box 38, Folder 391)
    - Multi-Year Renewals, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 392)
    - DAPs, general, 1972-1973 (Box 38, Folder 393)
    - FAPs, general, 1970-1972 (Box 38, Folder 394)
    - Report and Analysis, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 395)
    - Information Paper – Management and Program Trends, 1971 (Box 39, Folder 396)
    - Information Paper – FAP Project, 1971-1972 (Box 39, Folder 397)
    - Appropriation Reports, 1968 (Box 39, Folder 398)
  - Financial Reviews of Grantees
    - Stewart, Charles, 1966-1967 (Box 39, Folder 399)
    - Gregory, Stanley, 1969-1970 (Box 39, Folder 400)
    - Akmajian, Herant, 1969-1971 (Box 39, Folder 401)
    - Stewart, Charles, 1969 (Box 39, Folder 402)
    - Stewart, Charles, 1970 (Box 40, Folder 403)
    - Stewart, Charles, 1971 (Box 40, Folder 404)
    - Bishop, Jeremy and Charles Stewart, 1970 (Box 40, Folder 405)
    - Masone Jr., Nunzio, Ronald Esola, and Charles Stewart, 1970-1971 (Box 40, Folder 406)
    - Wolf, Thomas, 1970-1971 (Box 40, Folder 407)